### Keep Reading

### Company

### Sign Up for Your Weekly Digest  
to All Things Parenting

Made possible with support from The  
Support Of Ontario Creates  

[

](https://www.ontariocreates.ca/)

© 2022 ParentsCanada. All rights reserved.

[

.svg)

.svg)](https://www.facebook.com/ParentsCanada)[

.svg)

.svg)](https://twitter.com/ParentsCanada/)[

.svg)

.svg)](https://www.instagram.com/parentscanada/)[

.svg)

.svg)](https://www.youtube.com/user/ParentsCanada)

    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics

    [](#)[
    
    .svg)

    .svg)](https://www.facebook.com/ParentsCanada)[
    
    .svg)

    .svg)](https://twitter.com/ParentsCanada/)[
    
    .svg)

    .svg)](https://www.instagram.com/parentscanada/)[
    
    .svg)

    .svg)](https://www.youtube.com/user/ParentsCanada)

    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics
        
    * ### Topics

    [](#)[
    
    .svg)

    .svg)](https://www.facebook.com/ParentsCanada)[
    
    .svg)

    .svg)](https://twitter.com/ParentsCanada/)[
    
    .svg)

    .svg)](https://www.instagram.com/parentscanada/)[
    
    .svg)

    .svg)](https://www.youtube.com/user/ParentsCanada)

[Baby Names 2023](https://www.parentscanada.com/baby-naming-hub/)[Help Your Kids Succeed With Our Back To School Guide](https://www.parentscanada.com/help-your-kids-succeed-with-our-back-to-school-guide/)[Girls Empowering Girls](https://www.parentscanada.com/girls-empowering-girls/)[Baby At The Table – Recipe Ideas From Canada Beef](https://www.parentscanada.com/baby/baby-at-the-table-recipe-ideas-from-canada-beef/)[Ready, Set, Winter! A Guide To Staying Safe On The Road This Winter.](https://www.parentscanada.com/caa-winter-driving-tips/)[Microsoft Education & Technology Learning Hub](https://www.parentscanada.com/microsoft-education-technology-learning-hub/)[Baby & Child Care Encyclopedia – Read It Now!](https://www.parentscanada.com/bcce-book-2021/)[Must-Have Products](https://www.parentscanada.com/category/need-it/)[Calling All Dads!](https://www.parentscanada.com/category/sponsored/)

Privacy Pledge
==============

ParentsCanada takes your privacy seriously. We have developed this privacy statement to clearly outline how your personal information is used. The following discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices for the ParentsCanada.com website. ParentsCanada is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

### **Registration**

The ParentsCanada.com registration form requires you to give us certain contact information about yourself. We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences. Your information is kept strictly confidential and will only be used in the manner outlined in this statement. By registering with ParentsCanada you will receive a free monthly e-newsletter form ParentsCanada.com. As well, from time to time, you may receive additional promotional offers from carefully screened partners serving new and expectant parents, only if you have agreed to do so in the registration process. Any and all, electronic communications sent by us will be accompanied by an unsubscribe link. If you no longer wish to receive electronic communications from us, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions and we will no longer send to you.

### **Surveys And Contests**

From time to time we may run online surveys or contest on the site. In this context we may ask visitors for additional contact and demographic information (like their age, or income level). We use this data only for the purposes of the survey and/or contest, for example, to contact the winner. Other information will only be used by us or shared with others on an aggregate basis, unless you have specifically agreed to the release of your personal information.

### **Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends and administer the site. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### **  
Public Forms**

This site may make instant messaging, chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### **Links**

This site contains links to other sites. ParentsCanada.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of linked websites.

### **Unsubscribing**

If, at any time, you no longer wish to receive our newsletters or promotional materials from ParentsCanada or our partners, you may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of every email.

### **  
Contacting The Website**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us at: [admin@parentscanada.com](mailto:admin@parentscanada.com)

#### Made Possible With The Support Of Ontario Creates

[

](https://www.ontariocreates.ca/)

### Keep Reading

### Company

### Parenting is hard. We’re here to help  
with our FREE weekly newsletter!

[

.svg)

.svg)](https://www.facebook.com/ParentsCanada)[

.svg)

.svg)](https://twitter.com/ParentsCanada/)[

.svg)](https://www.instagram.com/parentscanada/)[

.svg)](https://www.youtube.com/user/ParentsCanada)

© 2024 ParentsCanada. All rights reserved.

Website Powered by The Influence Agency [

](https://theinfluenceagency.com/)
